(Leslie:)Wow.
(Leslie:)So I heard your relationship with Penny
crashed to the ground...
(Leslie:)...like blue ice
falling out of an airplane lavatory.
- Where'd you hear that?
- Actually, I read it. Wolowitz texted me.
"Like blue ice
falling out of an airplane lavatory," yep.
Yeah, I thought it was a pretty good one.
I gave him an "LOL."
(Leslie:)Anyway, it got me thinking.
(Leslie:)Now that you're unattached, maybe
we can revisit our previous attachment.
(Leonard:)Are you suggesting another bout
of stress release?
(Leslie:)No, I'm all done with casual sex.
(Leslie:)I'm fully committed
to the traditional relationship paradigm.
Really? What changed?
(Leslie:)There's just a time
in every woman's life...
(Leslie:)...when she gets tired of waking up
on a futon...
(Leslie:)...with a bunch of people
she doesn't know.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I can see how that would...
A bunch of people?
(Leslie:)Anyway, I just figure
it's time to slow things down...